Cinthia Muñoz J.

< R E S U M E/>



(+56) 9 53614910

https://cmunoz-portafolio.netlify.app

Cerro San Valentín, XI Región, Coyhaique

https://github.com/cinthimarce

03/07/1989



A Graphic Designer graduated from the Duoc UC Professional Institute, with experience in the commercial and educational sectors. Throughout my career, I have worked in graphic and technological fields, designing creative visual communication solutions, production areas, interfaces, and visual identity. Additionally, I have knowledge and experience in retail and Visual Merchandising, where I developed an understanding of micromerchandising and space design.

My professional interest, however, lies in Web Design and User Interface (UI), areas where I can combine creativity and technology to enhance user experience (UX). I am proficient in tools such as Photoshop, Illustrator, and Revit. I consider myself a multifaceted, versatile, flexible, and curious person.

Work Experience

CRISTALINO MULTIMEDIA (REMOTE)

MAY 2024 - AUGUST 2024

GRAPHIC WEB DESIGNER

- Supported in the development of web applications using Vue3, Nuxt3, and Tailwind (dashboard and UI interfaces), for a 4-month project.
- Created promotional graphic material for the internal social media of Cardif Bank.
- Edited photos and digital graphics.
- Programmed HTML templates.

Achievement: Contributed to the design of an insurance web application for a Peruvian bank called Alfin.



VISUAL MERCHANDISING

- Decorated interior spaces with inspirational styles or themes.
- Supported the implementation of visual merchandising materials (signage, POP materials, graphics, datasheets, removable pieces, accessories, etc.).
- Coordinated the setup of commercial campaigns and promotional events.
- Maintained store design standards.

Achievement: Led and collaborated with the store's MET team to improve the customer experience.

CONSULTORA ART (PROJECT ACCIONA, CNCA) COYHAIQUE. APRIL 2018 - DECEMBER 2020 ARTIST EDUCATOR

- Conducted diagnostic assessments in educational communities to identify issues to address with students from various schools and levels.
- Implemented artistic work methodologies, such as photography, muralism, recycling, pixel art, soundscapes, and stop motion, to stimulate observation, reflection, and emotional expression.
- Developed audiovisual records, reports, and progress reports for ongoing projects.
- Managed and coordinated final exhibitions of students' work through photographs, interventions, or other activities in educational spaces.

Achievement: Developed the artistic project "Las Sombras," which fostered students' creativity for SEA (Transforming the Present, Dreaming the Future) during the 2020 pandemic.

TEDOS, SANTIAGO. GRAPHIC DESIGNER

MAY 2014 - OCTOBER 2016

- Designed and created the corporate image of the company, including logos, stationery, and corporate videos.
- Developed creative visual communication solutions for mobile applications for iOS and Android, in collaboration with the IT department.

Achievement: Designed the UI for Mcheck, an app that improved the client company's efficiency by providing data and photographic work records.

Academic Background

FRONT-END TRAINEE Digital Talent Scholarship - Edutecno	2023
PROGRAM UX-UI Desafío Latam Academy	2022
DIPLOMA IN INTERIOR DESIGN University Andrés Bello	2021
GRAPHIC DESIGN IP Duoc UC, Concepción.	2013
HIGH SCHOOL Juan Pablo II Technical High School, Coyhaique	2006

Courses

BASIC ENGLISH COURSE YWAM Virginia Richmond U.S.A	2024
ONLINE COURSE REVIT FUNDAMENTALS Academy CDC	2021
ONLINE COURSE INTERDISCIPLINARY ARTISTIC EDUCATION University of Chile.	2020

Complementary Skills

LANGUAGES	English B1 Intermediate
SOFTWARE	Adobe Photoshop (Advanced) Adobe Illustrator (Advanced) Adobe Indesign (Intermediate) Adobe Premiere (Intermediate) Adobe Affter Effect, (Basic) Autocad (Basic) Revit (Basic) Visual Studio Code (Intermediate)
	Framework Vue (Intermediate)

TECHNICAL KNOWLEDGE

HTML5 (Advanced) CSS3 (Intermediate) Javascript (Basic) Framework Vue (Basic)

Tailwind (Basic) Nuxt3 (Basic)

Wordpress (Intermediate) Bootstrap (Intermediate)

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Basic experience in Photography, 3D Rendering, Murals,

Screen Printing, and Sewing.

Interest and skills in furniture design.

Driver's License (Class B). Availability to work remotely.

Willing to relocate.